const gradepre1data=[
    {
        question:"addiction",
        choices:["苦痛","中毒","添加物","適応"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"budget",
        choices:["道具","名札","予算","象徴"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"collision",
        choices:["競争","収集","衝突","混乱"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"depression",
        choices:["抑圧","圧縮","脱線","不景気"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"fraud",
        choices:["奇人","偽造","詐欺","凍結"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"rule out",
        choices:["除外する","支配する","反対する","判断を下す"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"give off",
        choices:["諦める","配る","放出する","譲歩する"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"fall for",
        choices:["落ちる","騙される","喧嘩する","転ぶ"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"run down",
        choices:["長引く","出会う","逃げる","荒廃する"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"brush off",
        choices:["復習する","掠める","無視する","赤面する"],
        answer:3
    }
]

export default gradepre1data;